Noticing nature and bird watching can help to slow you down
because you have to learn to be slower in order to notice the sounds,
the flapping of the wings, the rustle in the trees
What makes Flock unique is that
at the same time as being a Black founded collective
for a global majority of people,
challenging underrepresentation in the outdoors,
it also creatively brings people from
all walks of life on the journey,
which is incredible
I think Flock Together has reframed birdwatching as super cool,
and it's welcomed a lot of people
who might not have had it on their radar
into the space where they belong,
and yet it's really hopeful for the future